A Guide to the John D. Rockefeller, Sr. papers, Letterbooks, Series L FA431
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Letterbooks, 1877-1918; L; 389 Bound Volumes Volumes 1-381, 387-394.
  - Microfiche, 389 Bound Volumes Volumes 1-381, 387-394.
    - JDR Business and Office Files, 1879-1916; 1; 179 Bound Volumes Volumes 1-179
      - Volume 39, 1895 August 22-December 19 (Box 2)
      - Volume 40, 1895 December 20-1896 January 6 (Box 2)
      - Volume 41, 1896 January 7-April 4 (Box 2)
      - Volume 42, 1896 April 16-September 21 (Box 2)
      - Volume 43, 1896 September 21-1897 January 7 (Box 2)
      - Volume 44, 1897 May 24-July 30 (Box 2)
      - Volume 45, 1897 July 28-October 23 (Box 2)
      - Volume 46, 1897 October 23-December 17 (Box 2)
      - Volume 47, 1897 December 17-1898 February 17 (Box 2)
      - Volume 48, 1898 February 18-1898 April 22 (Box 2)
      - Volume 49, 1898 April 22-July 11 (Box 2)
      - Volume 50, 1898 July 12-September 29 (Box 2)
      - Volume 51, 1898 September 15-December 29 (Box 2)
      - Volume 52, 1898 December 15-1899 February 6 (Box 2)
      - Volume 53, 1899 February 6-April 6 (Box 2)
      - Volume 54, 1899 April 6-May 24 (Box 2)
      - Volume 55, 1899 May 24-August 2 (Box 2)
      - Volume 56, 1899 August 3-October 19 (Box 2)
      - Volume 57, 1899 October 19-December 21 (Box 2)
      - Volume 58, 1899 December 21-1900 February 20 (Box 2)
      - Volume 59, 1900 February 15-April 25 (Box 2)
      - Volume 60, 1900 April 25-June 27 (Box 2)
      - Volume 61, 1900 June 27-October 3 (Box 2)
      - Volume 62, 1900 October 3-December 4 (Box 2)
      - Volume 63, 1900 December 1-1901 January 14 (Box 3)
      - Volume 64, 1901 January 14-March 14 (Box 3)
      - Volume 65, 1901 March 14-May 11 (Box 3)
      - Volume 66, 1901 May 11-June 30 (Box 3)
      - Volume 67, 1901 July 1-October 24 (Box 3)
      - Volume 68, 1901 October 24-December 27 (Box 3)
      - Volume 69, 1901 December 27-1902 February 17 (Box 3)
      - Volume 70, 1902 February 19-April 12 (Box 3)
      - Volume 71, 1902 April 12-May 28 (Box 3)
      - Volume 72, 1902 May 29-July 17 (Box 3)
      - Volume 73, 1902 July 17-October 22 (Box 3)
      - Volume 74, 1902 October 22-December 13 (Box 3)
      - Volume 75, 1902 December 15-1903 January 20 (Box 3)
      - Volume 76, 1903 January 17-August 17 (Box 3)
      - Volume 77, 1903 March 18-May 27 (Box 3)
      - Volume 78, 1903 May 27-July 24 (Box 3)
      - Volume 79, 1903 July 25-October 6 (Box 3)
      - Volume 80, 1903 October 5-December 7 (Box 3)
      - Volume 81, 1903 December 5-1904 January 19 (Box 3)
      - Volume 82, 1904 January 19-March 19 (Box 3)
      - Volume 83, 1904 March 17-May 26 (Box 3)
      - Volume 84, 1904 May 27-August 22 (Box 3)
      - Volume 85, 1904 August 22-November 2 (Box 3)
      - Volume 86, 1904 November 2-January 7 (Box 3)
      - Volume 87, 1905 January 7-April 4 (Box 3)
      - Volume 88, 1905 April 4-May 27 (Box 3)
      - Volume 89, 1905 May 29-July 19 (Box 3)
      - Volume 90, 1905 July 19-September 15 (Box 3)
      - Volume 91, 1905 September 15-November 14 (Box 3)
      - Volume 92, 1905 November 14-December 26 (Box 3)
      - Volume 93, 1905 December 27-30 (Box 3)
      - Volume 94, 1906 January 2-February 3 (Box 3)
      - Volume 95, 1906 February 2-March 8 (Box 3)
      - Volume 96, 1906 March 9-April 12 (Box 4)
      - Volume 97, 1906 April 13-May 28 (Box 4)
      - Volume 98, 1906 May 29-July 31 (Box 4)
      - Volume 99, 1906 July 31-October 2 (Box 4)
      - Volume 100, 1906 October 2-November 19 (Box 4)
      - Volume 101, 1906 November 20-December 26 (Box 4)
      - Volume 102, 1906 December 27-1907 January 23 (Box 4)
      - Volume 103, 1907 January 23-February 19 (Box 4)
      - Volume 104, 1907 February 20-March 22 (Box 4)
      - Volume 105, 1907 March 23-April 20 (Box 4)
      - Volume 106, 1907 October 19-November 27 (Box 4)
      - Volume 107, 1907 November 29-1908 January 6 (Box 4)
      - Volume 108, 1908 January 6-February 10 (Box 4)
      - Volume 109, 1908 February 10-March 11 (Box 4)
      - Volume 110, 1908 March 12-April 9 (Box 4)
      - Volume 111, 1908 April 10-May 11 (Box 4)
      - Volume 112, 1908 May 11-June 10 (Box 4)
      - Volume 113, 1908 June 11-July 8 (Box 4)
      - Volume 114, 1908 July 10-August 21 (Box 4)
      - Volume 115, 1908 August 24-September 28 (Box 4)
      - Volume 116, 1908 September 8-October 30 (Box 4)
      - Volume 117, 1908 November 2-30 (Box 4)
      - Volume 118, 1908 December 1-30 (Box 4)
      - Volume 119, 1908 December 30-1909 January 22 (Box 4)
      - Volume 120, 1909 January 23-February 18 (Box 4)
      - Volume 121, 1909 February 18-March 15 (Box 4)
      - Volume 122, 1909 March 16-April 12 (Box 4)
      - Volume 123, 1909 April 12-May 13 (Box 4)
      - Volume 124, 1909 May 14-June 14 (Box 4)
      - Volume 125, 1909 June 15-July 12 (Box 4)
      - Volume 126, 1909 July 12-August 16 (Box 4)
      - Volume 127, 1909 August 17-October 13 (Box 4)
      - Volume 128, 1909 October 13-November 17 (Box 4)
      - Volume 129, 1909 November 17-December 18 (Box 4)
      - Volume 130, 1909 December 17-1910 January 20 (Box 4)
      - Volume 131, 1910 January 20-February 19 (Box 5)
      - Volume 132, 1910 February 21-March 16 (Box 5)
      - Volume 133, 1910 March 16-April 9 (Box 5)
      - Volume 134, 1910 April 9-May 9 (Box 5)
      - Volume 135, 1910 May 10-June 10 (Box 5)
      - Volume 136, 1910 June 10-July 16 (Box 5)
      - Volume 137, 1910 July 18-September 17 (Box 5)
      - Volume 138, 1910 September 19-November 11 (Box 5)
      - Volume 139, 1910 November 12-December 19 (Box 5)
      - Volume 140, 1910 December 16-1911 January 20 (Box 5)
      - Volume 141, 1911 January 24-March 2 (Box 5)
      - Volume 142, 1911 March 1-April 11 (Box 5)
      - Volume 142, 1911 April 12-June 15 (Box 5, Volume 143)
      - Volume 144, 1911 June 10-September 20 (Box 5)
      - Volume 145, 1911 September 20-November 22 (Box 5)
      - Volume 146, 1911 November 22-1912 January 11 (Box 5)
      - Volume 147, 1912 January 12-February 17 (Box 5)
      - Volume 148, 1912 February 19-March 22 (Box 5)
      - Volume 149, 1912 March 22-April 26 (Box 5)
      - Volume 150, 1912 April 26-May 29 (Box 5)
      - Volume 151, 1912 May 31-July 5 (Box 5)
      - Volume 152, 1912 July 5-September 24 (Box 5)
      - Volume 153, 1912 September 25-November 7 (Box 5)
      - Volume 154, 1912 November 8-December 13 (Box 5)
      - Volume 155, 1912 December 16-1913 January 15 (Box 5)
      - Volume 156, 1913 January 15-February 6 (Box 5)
      - Volume 157, 1913 February 6-March 6 (Box 5)
      - Volume 158, 1913 March 11-May 8 (Box 5)
      - Volume 159, 1913 May 9-June 19 (Box 5)
      - Volume 160, 1913 June 20-August 15 (Box 5)
      - Volume 161, 1913 August 6-October 1 (Box 5)
      - Volume 162, 1913 October 1-November 18 (Box 5)
      - Volume 163, 1913 November 19-December 29 (Box 5)
      - Volume 164, 1913 December 29-1914 February 2 (Box 5)
      - Volume 165, 1914 February 3-March 5 (Box 6)
      - Volume 166, 1914 March 6-April 8 (Box 6)
      - Volume 167, 1914 April 9-May 6 (Box 6)
      - Volume 168, 1914 May 6-21 (Box 6)
      - Volume 169, 1914 May 22-June 20 (Box 6)
      - Volume 170, 1914 June 23-August 3 (Box 6)
      - Volume 171, 1914 August 3-October 2 (Box 6)
      - Volume 172, 1914 October 2-November 10 (Box 6)
      - Volume 173, 1914 November 10-December 16 (Box 6)
      - Volume 174, 1914 December 16-1915 February 6 (Box 6)
      - Volume 175, 1915 February 8-April 1 (Box 6)
      - Volume 176, 1915 April 3-June 18 (Box 6)
      - Volume 177, 1915 June 18-November 9 (Box 6)
      - Volume 178, 1915 November 10-1916 March 20 (Box 6)
      - Volume 179, 1916 March 20-June 5 (Box 6)
    - JDR Business, 1877-1897; 2; 32 Bound Volumes Volumes 180-211
      These letterbooks document JDR's activities in the Standard Oil Company and other investments.
      - Volume 180, 1877 August 11-1878 January 12 (Box 6)
      - Volume 181, 1877 November 3-1878 January 10 (Box 6)
      - Volume 182, 1878 January 10-February 25 (Box 6)
      - Volume 183, 1878 February 25-April 25 (Box 6)
      - Volume 184, 1878 February 25-June 5 (Box 6)
      - Volume 185, 1879 February 25-May 29 (Box 6)
      - Volume 186, 1879 November 8-1881 May 18 (Box 6)
      - Volume 187, 1881 June 24-1882 May 3 (Box 6)
      - Volume 188, 1882 May 11-1884 December 31 (Box 6)
      - Volume 189, 1885 January 1-1886 March 13 (Box 6)
      - Volume 190, 1886 March 13-1888 March 28 (Box 6)
      - Volume 191, 1888 March 31-1890 October 3 (Box 6)
      - Volume 192, 1890 October 8-1893 December 22 (Box 6)
      - Volume 193, 1890 January 3-August 11 (Box 6)
      - Volume 194, 1891 February 6-July 31 (Box 6)
      - Volume 195, 1891 July 31-1892 February 24 (Box 6)
      - Volume 196, 1892 February 24-October 12 (Box 6)
      - Volume 197, 1892 October 13-1893 May 29 (Box 7)
      - Volume 198, 1893 May 29-October 31 (Box 7)
      - Volume 199, 1893 October 31-1894 March 14 (Box 7)
      - Volume 200, 1894 March 15-July 11 (Box 7)
      - Volume 201, 1894 July 12-October 24 (Box 7)
      - Volume 202, 1894 October 24-1895 February 5 (Box 7)
      - Volume 203, 1895 February 6-May 16 (Box 7)
      - Volume 204, 1895 May 16-October 5 (Box 7)
      - Volume 205, 1895 October 5-1986 February 1 (Box 7)
      - Volume 206, 1896 February 1-May 25 (Box 7)
      - Volume 207, 1896 May 26-October 15 (Box 7)
      - Volume 208, 1896 October 16-1897 January 27 (Box 7)
      - Volume 209, 1897 January 27-March 27 (Box 7)
      - Volume 210, 1897 March 27-May 24 (Box 7)
      - Volume 211, 1897 November 3-1899 March 6 (Box 7)
    - JDR Personal, 1904-1918; 3; 42 Bound Volumes Volumes 212-253
      These letterbooks cover JDR's activities as he saw them from outside the office after his retirement. They cover both business and philanthropy and include letters of instruction to the office.
      - Volume 212, 1904 June 17-December 7 (Box 7)
      - Volume 213, 1904 December 7-1905 April 25 (Box 7)
      - Volume 214, 1905 April 25-July 20 (Box 7)
      - Volume 215, 1905 July 20-October 24 (Box 7)
      - Volume 216, 1905 October 24-1906 January 11 (Box 7)
      - Volume 217, 1906 January 11-May 1 (Box 7)
      - Volume 218, 1906 October 16-1907 February 18 (Box 7)
      - Volume 219, 1906 May 1-October 16 (Box 7)
      - Volume 220, 1907 February 18-June 12 (Box 7)
      - Volume 221, 1907 June 13-October 4 (Box 7)
      - Volume 222, 1907 October 4-1908 January 8 (Box 7)
      - Volume 223, 1908 January 8-July 10 (Box 7)
      - Volume 224, 1908 July 11-October 8 (Box 7)
      - Volume 225, 1908 October 8-1909 February 12 (Box 7)
      - Volume 226, 1909 February 12-May 20 (Box 7)
      - Volume 227, 1909 May 21-August 23 (Box 7)
      - Volume 228, 1909 August 24-December 7 (Box 8)
      - Volume 229, 1909 December 7-1910 March 12 (Box 8)
      - Volume 230, 1910 March 13-June 15 (Box 8)
      - Volume 231, 1910 June 15-September 17 (Box 8)
      - Volume 232, 1910 September 17-1911 January 4 (Box 8)
      - Volume 233, 1911 January 5-April 25 (Box 8)
      - Volume 234, 1911 April 26-August 17 (Box 8)
      - Volume 235, 1911 August 17-November 20 (Box 8)
      - Volume 236, 1911 November 20-1912 February 3 (Box 8)
      - Volume 237, 1912 February 3-April 26 (Box 8)
      - Volume 238, 1912 April 26-July 15 (Box 8)
      - Volume 239, 1912 July 15-October 21 (Box 8)
      - Volume 240, 1912 October 21-1913 July 20 (Box 8)
      - Volume 241, 1913 January 20-May 2 (Box 8)
      - Volume 242, 1913 May 2-July 16 (Box 8)
      - Volume 243, 1913 July 16-November 18 (Box 8)
      - Volume 244, 1913 November 18-1914 April 10 (Box 8)
      - Volume 245, 1914 April 11-July 8 (Box 8)
      - Volume 246, 1914 July 8-September 21 (Box 8)
      - Volume 247, 1914 September 21-December 15 (Box 8)
      - Volume 248, 1914 December 15-1915 March 20 (Box 8)
      - Volume 249, 1915 March 23-July 14 (Box 8)
      - Volume 250, 1915 July 14-August 10 (Box 8)
      - Volume 251, 1915 September 21-November 19 (Box 8)
      - Volume 252, 1915 November 17-December 30 (Box 8)
      - Volume 253, 1918 January 2-May 9 (Box 8)
    - JDR Jr. Personal, 1897-1916; 4; 71 Bound Volumes Volumes 254-324
      These letterbooks reflect JDR Jr.'s growing participation in his father's affairs as well as the management of his own interests. These are not exclusively JDR Jr. letters but include letters by members of JDR's personal staff.
      - Volume 254, 1897 October 2-1898 September 27 (Box 8)
      - Volume 255, 1898 September 27-1899 May 16 (Box 8)
      - Volume 256, 1899 May 17-1900 May 1 (Box 8)
      - Volume 257, 1900 May 4-November 24 (Box 8)
      - Volume 258, 1900 November 26-1901 February 14 (Box 9)
      - Volume 259, 1901 February 14-June 11 (Box 9)
      - Volume 260, 1901 June 13-December 10 (Box 9)
      - Volume 261, 1901 December 11-1902 February 20 (Box 9)
      - Volume 262, 1902 February 20-June 24 (Box 9)
      - Volume 263, 1902 June 25-1903 January 29 (Box 9)
      - Volume 264, 1903 January 29-May 10 (Box 9)
      - Volume 265, 1903 May 12-November 10 (Box 9)
      - Volume 266, 1903 November 11-1904 March 24 (Box 9)
      - Volume 267, 1904 March 25-June 14 (Box 9)
      - Volume 268, 1904 June 14-November 9 (Box 9)
      - Volume 269, 1904 November 11-1905 June 1 (Box 9)
      - Volume 270, 1905 June 2-December 20 (Box 9)
      - Volume 271, 1905 December 21-1906 April 16 (Box 9)
      - Volume 272, 1906 April 16-November 8 (Box 9)
      - Volume 273, 1906 November 10-1907 March 25 (Box 9)
      - Volume 274, 1907 March 26-October 10 (Box 9)
      - Volume 275, 1907 April 22-May 31 (Box 9)
      - Volume 276, 1907 May 31-July 17 (Box 9)
      - Volume 277, 1907 July 18-September 5 (Box 9)
      - Volume 278, 1907 September 6-October 18 (Box 9)
      - Volume 279, 1907 October 14-1908 February 21 (Box 9)
      - Volume 280, 1908 February 21-May 21 (Box 9)
      - Volume 281, 1908 May 22-December 18 (Box 9)
      - Volume 282, 1908 December 21-1909 March 11 (Box 9)
      - Volume 283, 1909 March 12-June 26 (Box 9)
      - Volume 284, 1909 June 28-December 16 (Box 9)
      - Volume 285, 1909 December 17-1910 February 17 (Box 9)
      - Volume 286, 1910 February 17-April 19 (Box 9)
      - Volume 287, 1910 April 21-June 10 (Box 9)
      - Volume 288, 1910 June 13-September 16 (Box 9)
      - Volume 289, 1910 September 16-November 11 (Box 9)
      - Volume 290, 1910 November 12-December 29 (Box 9)
      - Volume 291, 1910 December 30-1911 January 23 (Box 10)
      - Volume 292, 1911 January 20-February 23 (Box 10)
      - Volume 293, 1911 February 24-March 24 (Box 10)
      - Volume 294, 1911 March 27-April 25 (Box 10)
      - Volume 295, 1911 April 27-June 2 (Box 10)
      - Volume 296, 1911 June 2-July 13 (Box 10)
      - Volume 297, 1911 July 13-September 8 (Box 10)
      - Volume 298, 1911 September 8-October 25 (Box 10)
      - Volume 299, 1911 October 26-December 14 (Box 10)
      - Volume 300, 1911 December 15-1912 January 23 (Box 10)
      - Volume 301, 1912 January 25-February 27 (Box 10)
      - Volume 302, 1912 February 28-April 3 (Box 10)
      - Volume 303, 1912 April 3-May 13 (Box 10)
      - Volume 304, 1912 May 13-June 24 (Box 10)
      - Volume 305, 1912 June 25-August 12 (Box 10)
      - Volume 306, 1912 August 12-October 16 (Box 10)
      - Volume 307, 1912 October 17-December 7 (Box 10)
      - Volume 308, 1912 December 9-1913 January 24 (Box 10)
      - Volume 309, 1913 January 24-March 11 (Box 10)
      - Volume 310, 1913 March 6-April 22 (Box 10)
      - Volume 311, 1913 April 22-May 28 (Box 10)
      - Volume 312, 1913 May 27-July 23 (Box 10)
      - Volume 313, 1913 July 24-September 30 (Box 10)
      - Volume 314, 1913 October 1-November 14 (Box 10)
      - Volume 315, 1913 November 14-December 22 (Box 10)
      - Volume 316, 1913 December 22-1914 January 27 (Box 10)
      - Volume 317, 1914 January 27-March 5 (Box 10)
      - Volume 318, 1914 March 6-April 14 (Box 10)
      - Volume 319, 1914 April 14-June 10 (Box 10)
      - Volume 320, 1914 June 9-September 25 (Box 10)
      - Volume 321, 1914 September 26-December 4 (Box 10)
      - Volume 322, 1914 December 4-1915 February 1 (Box 10)
      - Volume 323, 1915 February 3-June 17 (Box 11)
      - Volume 324, 1915 June 17-1916 June 3 (Box 11)
    - Abeyton Realty, 1909-1916; 5; 5 Bound Volumes Volumes 325-329
      Management of Cleveland properties through a real estate company.
      - Volume 325, 1909 June 5-1910 September 17 (Box 11)
      - Volume 326, 1910 September 20-1911 December 7 (Box 11)
      - Volume 327, 1911 December 8-1913 May 7 (Box 11)
      - Volume 328, 1913 May 7-1914 September 29 (Box 11)
      - Volume 329, 1914 September 30-1916 May 25 (Box 11)
    - JDR - Frederick T. Gates - Business, 1893-1905; 6; 12 Bound Volumes Volumes 330-341
      F.T. Gates management of JDR's principal investments. His responses to investment opportunities offered to JDR.
      - Volume 330, 1893 January 30-1894 April 2 (Box 11)
      - Volume 331, 1894 April 10-November 9 (Box 11)
      - Volume 332, 1894 November 10-1895 April 27 (Box 11)
      - Volume 333, 1895 April 29-September 30 (Box 11)
      - Volume 334, 1895 September 30-1896 June 29 (Box 11)
      - Volume 335, 1896 June 29-1897 April 7 (Box 11)
      - Volume 336, 1897 April 8-December 31 (Box 11)
      - Volume 337, 1898 January 1-1899 June 16 (Box 11)
      - Volume 338, 1899 June 20-1901 January 15 (Box 11)
      - Volume 339, 1901 January 16-1904 February 29 (Box 11)
      - Volume 340, 1904 March 4-1905 October 31 (Box 11)
      - Volume 341, 1905 November 1-1905 December 29 (Box 11)
    - JDR - Frederick T. Gates - Philanthropy, 1891-1905; 7; 11 Bound Volumes Volumes 342-352
      F.T. Gates as JDR's chief almoner. Investigations of worthy causes. Gifts and declinations.
      - Volume 342, 1891 December 5-1893 January 13 (Box 11)
      - Volume 343, 1893 January 17-1894 April 2 (Box 11)
      - Volume 344, 1894 April 9-1896 January 7 (Box 11)
      - Volume 345, 1896 January 7-1897 January 4 (Box 11)
      - Volume 346, 1897 January 5-1898 March 28 (Box 11)
      - Volume 347, 1898 March 28-1900 December 10 (Box 11)
      - Volume 348, 1900 December 12-1902 November 21 (Box 11)
      - Volume 349, 1902 November 21-1904 June 6 (Box 11)
      - Volume 350, 1904 June 10-1905 April 18 (Box 11)
      - Volume 351, 1905 April 18-November 2 (Box 11)
      - Volume 352, 1905 November 4-December 29 (Box 11)
    - Frederick T. Gates Personal, 1895-1913; 8; 9 Bound Volumes Volumes 353-361
      Strictly F.T. Gates affairs. Family fortunes, homes, relations.
      - Volume 353, 1895 September 4-1898 May 31 (Box 11)
      - Volume 354, 1898 January 7-1900 March 13 (Box 11)
      - Volume 355, 1900 March 13-1902 September 13 (Box 12)
      - Volume 356, 1902 September 15-1904 February 15 (Box 12)
      - Volume 357, 1904 February 17-1906 March 15 (Box 12)
      - Volume 358, 1906 March 15-1907 November 26 (Box 12)
      - Volume 359, 1907 November 27-1909 December 20 (Box 12)
      - Volume 360, 1909 December 20-1912 January 17 (Box 12)
      - Volume 361, 1912 January 17-1913 June 13 (Box 12)
    - Duluth, Missabe & Northern Railway Company, 1894-1904; 9; 6 Bound Volumes Volumes 362-366
      F.T. Gates managing railway company. Five annual reports to state railway commission.
      - Volume 362, 1894 February 14-1895 September 16 (Box 12)
      - Volume 363, 1895 September 20-1896 August 18 (Box 12)
      - Volume 364, 1896 August 21-1897 December 6 (Box 12)
      - Volume 365, 1897 December 7-1900 April 24 (Box 12)
      - Volume 366, 1900 April 24-1903 April 11 (Box 12)
    - Tilden Mining Company, 1896-1917; 10; 5 Bound Volumes Volumes 367-371
      - Volume 367, 1896 March-December (Box 12)
      - Volume 368, 1896 December 28-1897 November 1 (Box 12)
      - Volume 369, 1897 November 1-1898 May 13 (Box 12)
      - Volume 370, 1896 August 1-1903 July 10 (Box 12)
      - Volume 371, 1903 July 13-1917 January 25 (Box 12)
    - Lake Superior Consolidated Iron Mines, 1894-1899; 11; 5 Bound Volumes Volumes 372-376
      F.T. Gates managing the iron company.
      - Volume 372, 1894 February 14-October 26 (Box 12)
      - Volume 373, 1894 October 26-1895 August 23 (Box 12)
      - Volume 374, 1896 April 20-October 31 (Box 12)
      - Volume 375, 1896 November 2-1897 October 1 (Box 12)
      - Volume 376, 1898 June 10-1899 March 21 (Box 12)
    - Bessimer Steamship Company, 1896-1898; 12; 1 Bound Volumes Volume 377
      F.T. Gates managing the steamship company.
      - Volume 377, 1896 January 7-1898 February 1 (Box 12)
    - Everett & Monte Cristo Railway Company, 1894-1903; 13; 4 Bound Volumes Volumes 378-381
      F.T. Gates managing the railway company.
      - Volume 378, 1894 November 15-1898 January 17 (Box 12)
      - Volume 379, 1895 June 29-1897 January 23 (Box 12)
      - Volume 380, 1898 January 18-1901 July 2 (Box 12)
      - Volume 381, 1901 July 2-1903 August 20 (Box 12)
    - Starr J. Murphy, 1905-1908; 14; 1 Bound Volumes Volume 387
      Murphy, as G.E.B. secretary, handles college appeals.
      - Volume 387, 1905 August 25-1908 June 17 (Box 12)
    - Laura Spelman Rockefeller Estate, 1915-1916; 15; 1 Bound Volumes Volume 381
      - Volume 388, 1915 June 18-1916 June 5 (Box 12)
    - Receipt Book, 16
      - Volume 389 - Receipt Book (Box 12, Volume 389)
    - Standard Oil Company, 1885-1888; 17; 1 Bound Volumes Volume 390
      - Volume 390, 1885 June 5-1888 April 3 (Box 12)
    - William Rockefeller, 1871-1896; 18; 2 Bound Volumes Volumes 391-392
      - Volume 391, 1895 July 3-1896 January 30 (Box 12)
      - Volume 392, 1871 May 16-1876 March 9 (Box 12)
    - Rockefeller, Andrews and Flagler, 1867-1868; 19; 2 Bound Volumes Volumes 393-394
      - Volume 393, 1867 August 20-1868 March 20 (Box 12)
      - Volume 394, 1868 March 20-1868 September 9 (Box 12)